export const allQuestion = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Dirk%20the%20Daring",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Arthur",
            "Sir%20Toby%20Belch",
            "Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Animals",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Homo%20Sapiens",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Homo%20Ergaster",
            "Homo%20Erectus",
            "Homo%20Neanderthalensis"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Books",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Bilius",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Arthur", "John", "Dominic"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Comics",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Robert%20Kirkman",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Stan%20Lee",
            "Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson",
            "Robert%20Crumb"
        ]
    }

]



// allQuestion = [
//     {
//         question: "Which of the following is a client site language?",
//         a: "Java",
//         b: "C",
//         c: "Python",
//         d: "JavaScript",
//         correct: "d",
//     },
//     {
//         question: "What does HTML stand for?",
//         a: "Hypertext Markup Language",
//         b: "Cascading Style Sheet",
//         c: "Jason Object Notation",
//         d: "Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborginis",
//         correct: "a",
//     },
//     {
//         question: "What year was JavaScript launched?",
//         a: "1996",
//         b: "1995",
//         c: "1994",
//         d: "none of the above",
//         correct: "b",
//     },
//     {
//         question: "What does CSS stands for?",
//         a: "Hypertext Markup Language",
//         b: "Cascading Style Sheet",
//         c: "Jason Object Notation",
//         d: "Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborginis",
//         correct: "b",
//     }
// ]



// [
//     {
//         question: "Which of the following is a client site language?",
//         optionList: [
//             { ansOption: "Java", isCorrect: false },
//             { ansOption: "C", isCorrect: false },
//             { ansOption: "Python", isCorrect: false },
//             { ansOption: "JavaScript", isCorrect: true },
//         ]

//     },
//     {
//         question: "What does HTML stand for?",
//         optionList: [
//             { ansOption: "Hypertext Markup Language", isCorrect: true},
//             { ansOption: "Cascading Style Sheet", isCorrect: false },
//             { ansOption: "Jason Object Notation", isCorrect: false },
//             { ansOption: "Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborginis", isCorrect: false },
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         question: "What year was JavaScript launched?",
//         optionList: [
//             { ansOption: "1996", isCorrect: false },
//             { ansOption: "1995", isCorrect: true },
//             { ansOption: "1994", isCorrect: false },
//             { ansOption: "none of the above", isCorrect: false },
//         ]
//     },
//     {
//         question: "What does CSS stands for?",
//         optionList: [
//             { ansOption: "Hypertext Markup Language", isCorrect: false },
//             { ansOption: "Cascading Style Sheet", isCorrect: true },
//             { ansOption: "Jason Object Notation", isCorrect: false },
//             { ansOption: "Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborginis", isCorrect: false },
//         ]
//     }
// ]